





WHO AM I?

I am an Artificial Intelligence MSc graduate with experience in working with Deep Learning, Computer Vision, and Time Series Analysis in the medical domain.

My goal is to help you apply machine learning solutions to important problems.

SKILLS

Pytorch (Lightning) / Tensorboard / Slurm / Pandas / scikit-learn / pytest / gRPC / ONNX / H5PY / OpenSlide / NLTK / spaCy / Gensim / Docker / Singularity

EXPERIENCE

11/2021 - Now **Deep Learning Researcher**

Medis Medical Imaging

I researched, developed, and validated production-ready computer vision algorithms (Deep Learning-based and otherwise) for echocardiography workflow automation, and maintained and developed inference and evaluation infrastructure.

Pytorch (Lightning) / Slurm / scikit-learn / pytest / gRPC / ONNX

5/2021-7/2021 Artificial Intelligence Analyst

The Netherlands Cancer Institute

I investigated Deep Learning-based methods for outcome prediction of Ductal Carcinoma in Situ (DCIS) from pathology whole-slide images (WSIs).

Pytorch / Slurm / Docker / Singularity

11/2019 - 4/2021

Research Intern

The Netherlands Cancer Institute

Researched and developed a computational pipeline for predicting outcome of DCIS from WSIs.

Pytorch / Slurm / Docker / Singularity

6/2019 internship

internship

Research Intern

NLP and Data Mining project in collaboration with the University of Amsterdam.

scikit-learn / NLTK / spaCy / Gensim

3/2018 - 6/2018 **Teaching Assistant** University of Groningen

KPN

I assisted teaching for the BSc Neural Networks course at the University of Groningen.

internship

3/2018 - 8/2018

Research Intern

Universitair Medisch Centrum Groningen

I analysed biometric signals to perform early detection of sepsis in ICU patients.

scikit-learn

EDUCATION

2018 - 2021 MSc in Artificial Intelligence (Cum Laude) **University of Amsterdam**

I presented an abstract on my thesis Multiple-Instance Learning for Assessing Prognosis of Ductal Carcinoma In Situ at the European Congress of Pathology of 2021. Follow-up research based on my work was accepted at SPIE 2022.

2015 - 2018

BSc in Artificial Intelligence (Honours in Philosophy)

University of Groningen

I presented a paper resulting from my thesis on Early Detection of Sepsis Induced Deterioration Using Machine Learning at the BENELEARN2018 conference, and the paper was published in the conference proceedings.

SOFT SKILLS LANGUAGES **HOBBIES**

I am organized, detail oriented, good at team building and communication, and I have strong presentation skills.

English - C2 Italian - C2

I love cooking, playing bass, sailing, and kung fu.